indeedassessments.com 2017-11-13

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy explains how Prehire, Inc. and its affiliates and subsidiaries (“we,” “us,” or “Interviewed”) collects, uses, shares, and protects your Personal Information. This Privacy Policy applies to the information that we collect through the website located at https://interviewed.com,(the “Site”). “Personal Information” is information that could reasonably be used to identify you individually including but not limited to your name, e-mail address, phone number, IP address, and other identifying information. If you do not want us to handle your Personal Information in the manner described herein, do not use the Site. 

This Privacy Policy explains: 

– What information we collect 

– How we use that information 

– How we may disclose that information 

– Your choices regarding your Personal Information 

– Measure we take to keep your data secure 

As a guiding principal, our mission is to enable job seekers to prove their skills and present themselves as candidates to potential employers. 

This Privacy Policy will apply whether you are a “Visitor,” which means that you simply browse the Site, a “Candidate” on the Site, which means you are looking for a job or being evaluated by an employer and have registered with us and established an account (“Account”), or you are an employee, agent, contractor, or human resources professional of an employer that is using the Site to pre-screen potential employees (an “Employer”), operating in such capacity (in such case, an “Employer User”). Visitors, Candidates, Employer Users and Employers are individually referred to as a “User,” and collectively, as “Users”. 

1\. Information We Collect 

Personal Information: We receive and store information you voluntarily provide to us by using certain features of the Site, signing up and completing tests or job simulations, or otherwise using the features and functionality on the Site (the “Services”). When you register with us, regardless of whether you are a Candidate, Employer User or Employer, we require you to provide certain Personal Information. You may choose as part of certain Services to provide additional Personal Information. For example, if you are a Candidate updating your profile on the Site (“Profile”), we collect categories of information relevant to your Profile, including but not limited to your contact information, information about your professional experience, education, technical skills and desired salary. In addition, you may import resume, educational and other information from third party sites, and we will collect this information and associate it with you and your Profile. As we associate your answers and our analysis thereof with you and your Profile, we will consider it to be your Personal Information. We do all of this to help us in our effort to help you find the right Employer and the Employer the right Candidate. Please remember that you do not have to submit any of this additional information, but we may not be able to provide you certain Services without that information. 

If you are an Employer User, you may also submit information to us about your company, its job openings (including desired skill-sets and specific expertise), and your candidates. Some of this information may be made publicly available on the Site. Please remember that you do not have to submit any of this additional information, but we may not be able to provide you certain Services without such information. If you are a Candidate, an Employer may have provided information about you to initiate your candidacy or in connection with your use of Interviewed. We will collect this information about you, but this will NOT be considered your Personal Information. Each respective Employer will control this information. As a result, we will not provide you access to this information or the ability to use or control this information. 

Job Simulations and Tests: You may enroll to take certain assessments, tests, and job simulations on the Site (“Simulations”) in order to improve your Profile and apply for certain employment positions. By taking such Simulations, which Interviewed reserves the right to review and score in our sole discretion, you acknowledge that Interviewed may store, use, analyze, and disclose such Simulations and your performance in such Simulations at Interviewd’s sole discretion on the Site in connection with your Profile, Personal Information and our Services. 

“Automatically Collected” Information: When you access the Site or open one of our emails, we may automatically record certain information from your system by using different types of tracking technology. This “automatically collected” information may include Internet Protocol address (“IP Address”), a unique user ID, version of software installed, system type, the content and pages that you access on the Site, the dates and times that you visit the Site, and other information. 

“Cookies” Information: When you access the Site, we may send one or more cookies (small text files containing a string of alphanumeric characters) to your computer. Interviewed may use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie disappears after you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Site. Persistent cookies can be removed. Please review your web browser “Help” file to learn the best way to modify your cookie settings. 

Information from Other Sources: We may also obtain information, including Personal Information, from third parties and sources other than the Site, as well as from other Users of the Services. If we combine or associate information from such other sources with Personal Information that we collect through the Site, we will treat the combined information as Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

2\. The Way We Use Information 

We use the information we collect to serve our Users, consider Candidates, connect Candidates to Employers, market and promote our Services, and improve your experience on the Site. Some examples include: 

– Addressing service complaints 

– Communicating with you by email, telephone, or text message, in accordance with your wishes 

– Considering whether to link Candidates to Employers 

– Evaluating Candidate Simulations 

– Improving customer service 

– Sending you marketing and promotional emails, unless you have told us you do not want to receive such emails 

We may use your email address, without further consent, for administrative communications such as notifying you of major updates, for customer service purposes, and to send privacy or security related notices. 

Interviewed uses the information that we collect to understand the usage trends and preferences of our Users, to improve the way the Site works and looks, to create new products, services, features, and functionality. 

Interviewed may use “Automatically Collected” information and “Cookies” information to: (a) automatically update the Interviewed application on your system; (b) remember your information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you access the Site; (c) provide customized third-party advertisements, content and information; (d) monitor and report on the effectiveness of third-party marketing campaigns; (e) monitor and report aggregate usage metrics such as total number of visitors and pages accessed; and (d) track your entries, submissions, and status in any promotions or other activities. 

3\. When We Disclose Information 

Disclosure to Employers: For Candidate users, we may (and you hereby authorize us to) disclose your Personal Information to Employers in order to enable potential hiring Employers to find, evaluate, and hire you. The Site may allow Employers to view and search your profile on the Site. We do not control how Employers use or disclose information they obtain from us, including Personal Information. 

The information shared with such entities may include the information you have provided to us or that we have otherwise collected about you (whether from you or third-party sources) and any Simulations you have taken on the Site. 

We may disclose certain Personal Information: 

– To third party vendors who help us provide the Services, in which case the service providers are bound by their own individual privacy policies; 

– To third parties to whom you ask us to send Personal Information (including Employers and LinkedIn); 

– To a parent company, any subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control (collectively, “Affiliates”), in the event we have such Affiliates in the future, in which case the Affiliates will be bound by their own individual privacy policies; 

– If we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to (a) resolve disputes, investigate problems, or enforce our Terms of Use; (b) comply with relevant laws or to respond to requests from law enforcement or other government officials relating to investigations or alleged illegal activity, in which case we can (and you authorize us to) disclose Personal Information without subpoenas or warrants served on us; or (c) protect and defend our rights or property or the rights and property of you or third parties. 

We may disclose some limited User information to affiliated companies, contractors or other businesses or persons to: provide web site hosting, maintenance, and security services; fulfill orders; conduct data analysis and create reports; offer certain functionality; and assist Interviewed in improving the Site and creating new Services and features. 

We do not share your Personal Information with other organizations for their marketing or promotional uses without your prior express consent. Please be aware, however, that any Personal Information that you voluntarily choose to display on any publicly available portion of the Site becomes publicly available and may be collected and used by others without restriction. 

4\. Accessing And Controlling Your Information 

You may, of course, decline to share your Personal Information with us, in which case we will not be able to provide to you some of the Services found on the Site. 

You may correct and update information we collect from you by logging onto your Account and accessing your Profile. If you change or request changes to your information, subsequent uses or disclosures of that information by us will reflect those changes, however, we do not have the ability to update any information previously disclosed to any third party, including an Employer. 

We may take steps to verify your identity before providing you access to view, update, correct, or delete your Personal Information. Interviewed reserves the right to retain and use the information that we collect in a way that we believe, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to take precautions against liability; enforce our Terms of Service; or protect Interviewed or its users from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful uses. 

To protect your privacy and security, we may take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you Account access or making corrections to your information. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and Account information at all times. 

5\. Data Security 

We use commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards in an effort to preserve the integrity and security of your Personal Information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Interviewed, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, we make commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. 

If we learn of a security systems breach, we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. We may post a notice on the Site if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. 

6\. Children’s Privacy 

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, Interviewed does not knowingly collect or maintain Personal Information from persons under 13 years-of-age. If Interviewed learns that Personal Information of persons less than 13 years-of-age has been collected on or through the Site, then Interviewed will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. 

7\. In the Event of Merger or Sale 

In the event that Interviewed is acquired by or merged with a third-party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information that we have collected from Users as part of that merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. 

8\. Third Parties 

Except as otherwise expressly provided, this document addresses only the use and disclosure of information we collect from you or that you disclose to us. If you disclose your information to others besides Interviewed, whether they are users of the Site or on other sites or services, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. We do not control the privacy policies of third parties, and you are subject to the privacy policies of those third parties where applicable. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your Personal Information to others. 

9\. Changes and Updates to this Privacy Policy 

This Privacy Policy may be revised periodically without further notice to you and this will be reflected by a “last modified” date below. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. In general, we only use your Personal Information in the manner described in the Privacy Policy in effect when we received that Personal Information. Your continued use on the Site and the Services constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any future revisions. 

Created Date: 2015-07-01 

Last Modified Date: 2017-07-17
